Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, administrative records
1920-2017
RU 129
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
267.92
447 boxes
1216
The records consist of administrative files documenting the operations of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives at Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and departmental libraries and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files documenting the operations of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives at Yale University Library.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Archives; Libraries -- Special collections; Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Jane Hill, Librarian Yale Memorabilia, circa 1935-1952; Accession 19ND-A-414 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Yale dissertations legal files, permissions to microfilm, circa 1970s-1990s; Accession 19ND-A-428 (Box 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035.
- University Archives RLIN worksheets and problem documentation, circa 1984-1989; Accession 19ND-A-445
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024.
  - Yale Record Group (YRG)
    - 1-13, circa 1984-1989 (Box 1)
    - 14-38, circa 1984-1989 (Box 2)
    - 39-49, circa 1984-1989 (Box 3)
- Administrative records documenting the Architectural Archives project, circa 1980s-1990s; Accession 19ND-A-497
  - Corrspondence, cataloging worksheets, memos, etc. (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
- Plumbing and electrical architectural drawings for MSS&A dept. areas, 1928-1929; Accession 1986-A-082
  - PLUMBING
    - Basement Plan, Front Portion, 1928 March 5 (Box 1)
    - First Mezzanine Plan, Front Portion, 1928 March 5 (Box 1)
    - First Floor Plan, Front Portion, 1928 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Riser Sheet No. 1, 1928 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Basement, 126 High Street Addition, 1929 April 16 (Box 1)
    - 1st Floor, 126 High Street Addition, 1929 April 16 (Box 1)
    - 1st Floor Mezzanine, 126 High Street Addition, 1929 April 16 (Box 1)
    - 2nd Floor, 126 High Street Addition, 1929 April 16 (Box 1)
    - 3rd Floor, 126 High Street Addition, 1929 April 16 (Box 1)
    - Roof Plan, 126 High Street Addition, 1929 April 16 (Box 1)
    - Riser Plan, 126 High Street Addition, 1929 April 16 (Box 1)
  - ELECTRICAL
    - 1st Floor Plan Front, 1928 March 29 (Box 1)
    - 1st Story Mezzanine Plan Front, 1928 March 29 (Box 1)
    - Basement Plan Front, 1928 March 29 (Box 1)
    - Alteration at 126 High Street, 1929 May 22 (Box 1)
- University records management survey, 1978-1980; Accession 1993-A-082
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2016.
  - YRG 2 Presidential Records, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Records of the Provost, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Deputy Provost and Associate Provosts, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Grants and Contracts Administration, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Corporate and Foundation Relations, Office of, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Institutional Research, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Audio Visual Center, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Committee of Archeology, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Division of Humanities, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Division of the Sciences, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Division-of the Social Sciences, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Council on African Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Council on East Asian studies, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: International Relations, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Council on Latin American studies, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Council on Russian and East European studies, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Council on South East Asian studies, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Southern Africa Research Program, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost: Council on west European Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 3 Provost:.Language Lab, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 4 Secretary: Office of Public Information, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 University Auditing, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Director of Adminlstrat~ve Services, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Personnel, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and APministration: Printing Services, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Director ASA, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Parking and Communications, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Parking, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Communications, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Associated Student Agency, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Administrative Research Office, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: operations, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Grounds Maintenance, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Physical Plant, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Dining Halls, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: custodial Services and Housing, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Support Services and Employee Relations, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Engineering and utility Services, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 5 Finance and Administration: Construction Management, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 7 Development: Yale Alumni Fund, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 7 Development: Campaign for Yale, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 8 Yale Alumni Magazine, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 8 Association of Yale Alumni, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 8 Alumni Placement Service, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 8 Institutional Relations and Alumni programs., 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 8 Alumni Records Office, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 8 Alumni Association: Baseball, Football, Etc..., 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 9 Deans Records, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 9 Yale college: Associate and Assistant Deans, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 9 Yale college: University Career Services, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 9 Yale college: Undergraduate Affairs, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 9 Yale College: Education of Women, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 9 Yale college: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 9 Yale College: Special Undergraduate Program In the Humanities, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 11 Undergraduate Admissions: Admissions, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 11 Undergraduate Admissions: Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Council of Masters, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Residential college Seminar Office, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Berkeley College, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Brandford College, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Calhoun co~lege-, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Davenport College, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Timothy Dwight college, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Jonathan Edwards college, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Morse college, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Pierson College, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Saybrook College, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Silliman college, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Ezra Stiles College, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 13 Trumbull College, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Divinity School: R.ec;.ords of the Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Divinity School: Associate Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Divinity School: Admissions, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Divinity School: Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Divinity School: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Berkeley Divinity School and Center: Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Berkeley Diyinity School and Center:, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 21 Field Placement Service .., 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - YRG 14 Divinity School: Visual Education Service, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Afro-American Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 AElerican studies, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Anthropology, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 ~.stronomy, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Astronomy Observatory, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Biology, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Chemistry, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Classics, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Comparative Literature, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 computer Science, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 East Asian Languages and Literatures, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Economics, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Engineering and Applied Science, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 English, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Geology and Geophysics, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 History, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 History of Art, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 History of Science, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Linguistics, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Literature, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Mathematics, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Medieval Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Modern studies, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Music, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Philosophy, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Physics, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Physics Laboratories, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Political Science, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Psychology, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Renaissance studies, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 Sociology, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 14 statistic;s, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - YRG 15 Summer Programs: Office of the Director, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 15 Summer Language Institute, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 15 Summer Programs: English Language and Program For International Students, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 15 Summer School of Music and Art, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 19 School of Architecture: Records of the Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 19 School of Architecture: Admissions, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 19 School of Architecture: Alumni Office, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 19 School of Architecture: Director of Undergraduate studies, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 19 School of Architecture: Financial Aid and Business Office, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 19 School of Architecture: R~gistrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: Associate Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: -Admissions, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: Alumni 'Records and Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: Business Manager, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: .Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: Â·Graphic Design, and Photography, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: Yale Films (Formerly: Media. Design studio), 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 20 School of Art: Art and Architecture Gallery Drama School, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 22 Drama School: Records of the Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 22 Drama School: AcIm:issions, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 22 Drama School: Business Office, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 22 Drama School: Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 22 Drama School: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 22 Drama School: DepartmentjSchool/Theater/productions, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 23 Scho.9l of Engineering: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 24 School of Forestry: Records of the Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 24 School of Forestry: Associate and Assistant Deans, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 24 School of Forestry: Alumni, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 24 School of Forestry: Business Office, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 24 School of Forestry: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 25 Graduate School: Records of the Dean Graduate School: Admissions, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 25 Graduate School: Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 25 Graduate School: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law school: Records of the Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Associate and Assistant Deans, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Appointment Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Admissions, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law school: Alumni, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Business Manager, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Editor, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Library, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law school: Placement Office, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 26 Law School: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Deputy Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Ass~ciated Deans for Student Affairs, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Admissions, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: community Relations, Alumni Affairs and Government, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Development, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Facilities Planning, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Financial Affairs and Management, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Graduate and continuing Education, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Grant and Contract Administration, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 ~chool of Medicine: Human Investigation committee, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Medical Scientist Training prog., 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Office of Professional Services, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Women in Medicine, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Anesthesiology, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Yale comprehensive Cancer Center and division of Oncology, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Cell -Biolology, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Child study Center, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Comparative Medicine: Division of Animal Care, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Dermatology, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Diagnostic Radiology, 1978-1980 (Box 4)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Chairman, and Public Health Epidemiology, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Business Manager, Epidemiology and public Health, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Assistant Dean of curriculums, Epidemiology and Public Health, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Financial Aid, Epidemiology and Public Health, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Library, Epidemiology and public Health, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Registrar, Epidemiology and Public Health, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27. School of Medicine: History of Medicine, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Human Genetics, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: History of Medicine Curricula, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 school of Medicine: Internal~Medicine, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Clinical Scho~ars Program, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 Internal Medicine, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Laboratory Medicine, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Neuroanatomy, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Neurology, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Opthamology and Visual Science, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Pathology, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School oe Medicine: Pediatrics, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Pharmacology, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Section of Physical Sciences, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Phy~ician Associate program, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 school of Medicine: Physiology, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Psychiatry, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Yale Psychiatric Institute, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Surgery, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 27 School of Medicine: Therapeutic Radiology, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 28 School of Music: Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 28 School of Music: Admission, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 28 School of Music: Registrar, Financia1 Aid, Alumni '. J School of Music: Concert Office, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 28 School of Music: Financial Office, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Alumni, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Business Manager, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Financial Aid, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of ~ursirig: Basic Three Year Program, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: COmmunity Health Nursing, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Maternal Newborn Nursing, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing; Medical Surgical Nursing, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Pediatric Nursing, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Psychiatric Mental Health Nursing, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 29 School of Nursing: Research Program, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 30 School of Organization and Management: Dean, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 30 School of Organization and Management: Alumni Affairs, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 30 School of Organization and Management: Financial Aid and Business, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 30 School of Organization and Management: Registrar, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 30 School of Organization and Management: Professional studies, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 30 School of Organization and Management: Administrative Sciences, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Council on the Library and Museums, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Records of the University Librarian, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Associate Librarian for collection, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Development Materials, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: African Collection, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: East Asian Collection, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Slavic and East European Collection, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: southeast Asia Collection, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Bibliography, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Latin ~erican Collection, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32. Library: Associate Librarian for public Services, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: SML Reference, Inter-Library Loan, Newspaper, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Government Documents, Publications, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: SML Circulation, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library:.cross Campus Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Photo Services, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Historical Sound Recordings, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Hap Collection, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Associate Librarian for Technical Services, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Conservation, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Cataloging, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Acquisitions, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Preparations, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Business Office, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Budget Officer, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Building Service and security, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Payroll, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Purchasing and Supplies, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Personnel, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: standing Advisory Committee on Personnel, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: systems Office, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Manuscripts and Archives, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: staff Association, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Managerial and Professional staff Assoc., 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Factories & Projects, Babylonian collctn., 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Kline Science Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Anthropology Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Chemistry Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Engineering and Applied Science Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Geology Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Mathematics Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Social Science Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Statistics Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Art and Architecture Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Classics Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Divinity Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Drama Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Forestry and Environmental Studies Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Medical Library (Historical and Modern), 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 32 Library: Music Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - YRG 33 Peabody Museum, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 33 Art Gallery, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 33 Yale Center for British Art and Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 33 Musical Instruments Collection, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 34 University Press, Records of the Director, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 35 Health Services Center, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 35 Health Services, Director's Records, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 35 Health Services: occupation & Environment Health, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Yale China, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Information and Counseling Services for Women, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Information and Coun~eling Services for Women: New careers. for Women, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Economic Growth Center, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Institute of Far Eastern Languages, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 National Humanities Institute, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Institute of Sacred Music, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Institute for Social and Policy Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Yale-New Haven Teachers' Association, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 American Oriental Society, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 37 Cowles Foundation, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 38 Department of Athletics: Director, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 38 Department of Athletics: Associate Director, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 38 Department of Athletics: Financial Manager, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 38 Department of Athletics: Sports Information Office, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 39 Dwight Hall, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 39 Hillel Foundation, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 39 Yale Foreign Mis~ionary Band, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 40 Yale Clubs: WYBC, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 40 Yale Clubs: Aviation club, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
  - YRG 44 Publications: The Yale Review, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
- Records of grants, publications, and other projects, circa 1976-1990; Accession 1994-A-004
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026.
  - Grants, 1977-1982 (Box 1)
  - Grants Summary, 1978-79 (Box 1)
  - Publications: Kraus-Thomson organization Ltd., 7/78-3/79 (Box 1)
  - Asakawa Papers Microfilming Project 1986, 12/85-8/86 (Box 1)
  - Astronomy Dept. Microfilming - Frank Schlesinger Papers, 5/80-11/80 (Box 1)
  - Walter Camp Project: Stangeland, James, 9/78-12/80 (Box 1)
  - Walter Camp Project: Correspondence with other contributors and supporters, 10/78-12/79 (Box 1)